It's like a Dr. Seuss book, cutting down
trees to make room for the surveillance
cameras. There used to be oak trees all
down Broad Street in Augusta, and now
they're gone. This is like The Giving
Tree, man. Those trees have been here
since 1738 when James Oglethorpe founded
this place. Every single tree is gone.
Every single one is gone. They just cut
them all down. But the cameras, they're
new. Why the hell would you just cut
down trees for no reason? They provide
shade, they make oxygen. Some folks will
call me a conspiracy theorist, but the
only reason I can see that they would
cut down an old tree is to make way for
a new camera.
So all these new flock cameras can see
all the way down Broad Street. Cuz you
know, the cybersecurity center of all of
America is located right down this road.
It's like a Dr. Seuss book, cutting down
trees to make room for the surveillance
cameras.